As autumn
approaches and the leaves blanket
the dirt road winding through Four Oaks.
The season changes on the farm.
The air turns crisp,
carrying the smoky scent of chimneys
and the mouthwatering aroma of homemade
cooking.
Chat and ribbit perched by a nearby tree.
Their eyes wide with curiosity, drawn
by the irresistible aroma of food.
Chat and ribbit quietly tiptoe inside.
Through an open window of miracles.
Make sure you knead the dough firm.
Meera helps her mother with baking.
She rested the dough roller down.
When she catches sight of her two
furry friends peeking
curiously around the corner,
Hi chat and ribbit.
Why are you peeking around the corner?
Oh, you smell the food.
Well, it's Thanksgiving,
and it's a time to spend time
with family and to be grateful
for all that God has done for you.
We still have a whole lot to cook
and we're running out of time.
Meera. Come here for a second. Gotta go.
Coming, mom.
We have to invite our friends.
chat and Rabbit busily assist
with Thanksgiving cooking
and then flitting and hopping about
as they spread the exciting news
to all their friends on the farm.
All the farm animals
happily make their way to Miracle's
house, ready
to celebrate with one another.
From the waddling pigs
to the trotting cows.
They eagerly follow the dirt road.
Excited to see
what the festive gathering has in store.
Hurry.
Let's not keep everyone waiting.
The animals gathered around the table
enjoying fresh apples, warm
bread and pumpkin pie.
As we are reminded in life.
Be anxious for nothing, but in everything
by prayer and supplication,
with thanksgiving,
let your requests be made known to God
and the peace of God,
which surpasses all understanding,
will guard your hearts
and minds through Christ Jesus.